[{"answer": "I can't help it, honey, the ball just keeps goin' cocky wobbly on me..", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I did, didn' I, El", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Can I get you anything else", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Five'll do it", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Well, my friend and my friend, it sure is nice talking to you girls. I just wish I had more time..", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " A wig", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Yeah, but I can see a little bitty of the net up there, that's what give it away", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " It is him, he said it's him.  Aren't you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "that place, come on now...  Be a good girl", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm not going to get up an' leave you.  Now let's go over to my friend's an' have a good time", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How far are you going to", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "We'll get off in that place and hook another ride", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "that place? Are you on vacation", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "that place? Are you on vacation", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Cleaner than what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Cleaner than what", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "How do you know it's clean", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Salesmen and cops are the ones. If you'd ever waitressed, honey, you'd know", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Don't call me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I wouldn't be a waitress. They're nasty and full of crap", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Hold onto this", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No substitutions", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " No. We have tomatoes", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What does that mean? You don't have any tomatoes", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "But I can't have any. Is that what you mean", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Wait, I've made up my mind. I want a plain omelette, forget the tomatoes, don't put potatoes on the plate, and give me a side of wheat toast and a cup of coffee", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What do you mean, you don't have side orders of toast? You make sandwiches, don't you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Now all you have to do is hold the chicken, bring me the toast, charge me for the sandwich, and you haven't broken any rules", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah. I want you to hold it between your knees", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think that's true", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Besides being very rude", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, my,", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I hope I didn't hear that", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " The day after tomorrow", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah, I'll probably be free", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter. It was the feeling I was affected by", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You had no inner feeling", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You think I'm a fake", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No, it isn't what I think", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "It's convenient to fake looking for something right now, isn't it", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Some bath oil", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What about this one?  Or this one?  How about some jasmine?  What about some musk", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " What are you doing, screwing around with this crap?", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I don't find your language that charming", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'd like you to leave now. Is that direct enough", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Will you let me talk to you, please", "docId": "Five-Easy-Pieces.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " Oh. You have to tell me that", "qsentId": 48}]